You take online privacy seriously and so does BestAutoLenders2020.com. We are committed to protecting the personal information of visitors to our websites. This policy is one way of sustaining your trust in our company, our products and our services.

This online privacy policy applies only to the BestAutoLenders2020.com websites from which directly link to this policy. This policy applies only to the collection, use and sharing of information you provide online.

Our online privacy policy describes the information we collect from and about you during your visit to our websites. It also describes how we use information about you, whom we share it with, and how we protect it.

Our websites may contain links to third party sites not controlled by BestAutoLenders2020.com or covered by this online privacy policy. We recommend that you check the privacy statement of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.

Once you become a customer of BestAutoLenders2020.com, and annually thereafter while you remain a customer of BestAutoLenders2020.com, we will provide you with a Privacy Notice describing our privacy practices related to the collection and sharing of personal information about our customers, as required by law.

What personal information does BestAutoLenders2020.com collect online?

We collect personal information about you from the information you provide to us when you visit our websites.

The information will depend on the BestAutoLenders2020.com website you visit. This information may include, but is not limited to:

* Name
* Address
* Social Security number in whole or in part
* Phone numbers (including mobile)
* Account number
* Account number at a bank or other financial institution, type of bank account, and the name of bank or other financial institution
* Demand Note number
* Email address
* Email referral information
* Date of birth
* Current residential information including mortgage or rent payments
* Employment information
* Income information

**How does BestAutoLenders2020.com use the information it collects online?**

We use the personal information we collect online to process your request for services, products or information, to improve our customer service and products, and to facilitate your participation in online activities. For example, we may use the information you provide when you complete an online application for a product or service in order to process and evaluate your application. If you request product information, we may use the information you provide to mail you information you request.

We may also use the information we collect for analytic purposes, market research, or for marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

**Does BestAutoLenders2020.com share the personal information it collects online?**

We may share some of the information we collect about you with third parties, such as companies performing services on our behalf, to provide the products or services you have requested.

As permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you with companies with whom we have formal agreements to offer you financial products and services.

We may also share information about you with our affiliates (other companies in the BestAutoLenders2020.com family) and with non-affiliates for analysis, market research and marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

We may disclose your personal information as otherwise permitted or required by law.

**Does BestAutoLenders2020.com use cookies or other online technologies to collect information?**

When you browse or visit one of our websites, we may store certain information on your computer. This information may be in the form of a small text file called a “cookie” and can help us to tailor our sites to your individual preferences and save you time if you visit the site again. For example, cookies may be used to remember your bank or auto login preference. Where our websites support it, to save you time we may offer you the option to save your username and/or remember your computer by putting a cookie on your machine.

We may also use cookie technology or other online tracking technologies, like web beacons, to gather anonymous, aggregate information about your visit to our websites. This information allows us to measure site activity and to create ideas for improving our sites and may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, the website you visited just before coming to ours and your internet service provider. If we provide you with a link from a BestAutoLenders2020.com site to another site, we may track the fact that you clicked the link. This will help us understand which links are helpful to you when you visit our site, and will help us provide you with links that may be of interest to you, when you visit our site again.

When you visit our site, we capture data on which site pages you visited, when you visited that page and how long you were on the page, and the order in which you visited the pages. This information enables us to better understand your interests based on your prior online activities or preferences. We may use this information for analytic purposes, market research, or for marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

We may also use Flash objects (sometimes called “Local Shared Objects”) as part of our online authentication measures if you ask us to remember your computer. Flash objects help us recognize your computer when you come back to our site. We do not use Flash objects for any online behavioral advertising purpose.

You can disallow cookies by making the appropriate selection from your browser options to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. However, if you set your browser options to disallow cookies, you may limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our site, including challenges when accessing an account online. Deleting cookies does not delete Flash objects.

**How can I change or update the personal information BestAutoLenders2020.com collected about me online?**

If you have questions about information you provided on BestAutoLenders2020.com, call the phone number or select the “Contact Us” link provided on the specific website, so that we may assist you.

**What steps does BestAutoLenders2020.com take to protect personal information it collects online?**

We restrict access to the information obtained from our website to only those employees, agents and contractors who need access to do their jobs. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect your personal information.

Companies that provide online services on our behalf are required by contract to protect customer information, and are only allowed to use the information for the purpose of providing the services we have contracted with them to provide.

**Does BestAutoLenders2020.com collect personal information online about children?**

We don’t intentionally collect data or maintain data from children under 13 unless the personal information is provided by an adult. Our websites are not intended for children under 13.

**Does BestAutoLenders2020.com make public forums available on its websites?**

Public forums are available on our websites, which may include the ability to upload text, photographs and videos that are accessible to the general public. Unless we tell you otherwise, any information you disclose in these areas may become public information. You should use caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.

**California Consumer Privacy Act**

BestAutoLenders2020.com offers this service to help you shop for automobiles online. We will share the information you provide with the dealers and brands that you select. They will contact you to go over pricing and incentives for your vehicle selection(s). By using these services, you consent to us sharing the information you provide with these third parties, and you accept the terms outlined in our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

**Will BestAutoLenders2020.com make changes to this online privacy policy?**

This policy is effective January 30, 2013. We reserve the right to alter this policy at our discretion. Any change to this policy will be posted on our websites in a timely manner.

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have questions about this Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to know how we disclose personal information to third parties in connection with their direct marketing purposes, please don't hesitate to e-mail or post mail using the information stated below:

**E-mail**[info@BestAutoLenders.com](mailto:info@bestautolenders.com)

**Address**  
BestAutoLenders2020.com  
1614 Tower Way  
Superior, WI 54880

Advertisement
